https://www.europalawpublishing.com/customer-service/privacy-cookie-usage

Webshop
Journals online
Sign in
Shopping cart
(0)
Practice areas
Administrative LawComparative LawConstitutional LawCriminal LawDutch language titlesEconomic RegulationEnvironmental lawEuropean LawGeneralLaw of the SeaLegal HistoryLegal Theory
Series
The Avosetta SeriesEuropean Studies in Private LawThe Hogendorp PapersEuropean Administrative Law Series
Home
Customer service
Privacy policy & cookies
Privacy policy and cookies
Privacy policyThis privacy policy sets out how Europa Law Publishing uses and protects any information that you give Europa Law Publishing when you use this website.Europa Law Publishing is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Europa Law Publishing may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.  What we collectWe may collect the following information:• name and job title• contact information including email address• demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests• other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:• Internal record keeping.• We may use the information to improve our products and services.• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phoneor mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. How we use cookies A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Google cookiesEuropa Law Publishing uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store and use this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.
